topazlabs.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy – Topaz Labs

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or email support.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
  2. To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
  3. To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs
  4. To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  5. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  6. To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, just click the “Manage My Subscription” or “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each newsletter or email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s (Paypal) database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We absolutely do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### DMCA Policy

Please also visit our DMCA Policy section for our policies and reporting procedures regarding intellectual property rights and other proprietary rights of others.

### GDPR Compliance

  * Representative & DPO: [Joe Fedric](https://help.topazlabs.com/hc/requests/new), Webmaster & Head of Support
  * Contact: [Topaz Help Center](https://help.topazlabs.com/hc/requests/new)
  * Data Transfer: Topaz Labs does not share your data with  _any_ third parties that are not strictly necessary to conduct our business

Full details on Topaz Labs’ compliance with GDPR can be found here.  The information you provide us for processing is necessary for the functionality of our products.  We do not keep profiling information on individual customers, nor do we employ automatic decision making for any element of our business including prices, services, or products.  All of your personal data is collected directly from you, we don’t use sneaky practices to gather your personal data.  We just want to make awesome software for our wonderful customers.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 24, 2018.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Topaz Labs  
14285 Midway Rd., Ste. 125  
Addison, TX 75001  
info@topazlabs.com

### All Policies

  1. Terms & Conditions (this page)
  2. DMCA Policy
  3. GDPR Policy
  4. Privacy Policy
